--- Row Counts ---
distortion_label
Magnification and Catastrophizing    80
Black & White Thinking               80
Personalization                      80
Should Statements                    76
Emotional Reasoning                  75
Mental Filter                        75
Overgeneralization                   64
Jumping to Conclusions               55
No Distortion                        50
Name: count, dtype: int64

--- Trigger Word Percentages ---
distortion_label
Black & White Thinking                0.0
Emotional Reasoning                  26.7
Jumping to Conclusions                0.0
Magnification and Catastrophizing     0.0
Mental Filter                        16.0
No Distortion                        20.0
Overgeneralization                    0.0
Personalization                       0.0
Should Statements                    40.8
Name: text, dtype: float64

--- 15-Row Sample ---
['I see myself as a failure because of this one missed opportunity. Everything else seems insignificant in comparison.', "Every time I try to talk to my crush, they change the subject or pretend like we're not even talking about anything important. This is getting ridiculous.", "My muscles are tensed just thinking about this exam. Maybe that means I'm already doomed to fail.", "I wish someone could explain why some people are so critical all the time. Like, can't we just have constructive feedback without it being a personal attack?", "The more I try to achieve my goals, the more I feel overwhelmed by self-doubt. What if I'm just deluding myself?", "I keep thinking about the one thing that really hurts, and wondering why it still lingers in my mind so much. Maybe it's time to let go.", 'My friend told me she was nervous about the presentation. "It\'s not going to be a disaster," I said. "Just take some deep breaths and go with the flow."', "I've been trying to fix my car for weeks, but nothing seems to be working. Maybe I'll just have to sell it off before it's too late.", "I'm sure my team is secretly planning something without telling me, just like they did last time.", "When I see people doing better than me, I feel this sinking feeling in my stomach û like I'm already defeated.", "What would it be like to have everything work out perfectly? I suppose it's nice to imagine that, but in reality, there are ups and downs to life.", 'What if this audition goes terribly wrong and I humiliate myself on national TV?', "I tried something new today, and it didn't go well. Guess that confirms what I already knew û I'm not cut out for this.", "I've been late to work three days this week, it's a slippery slope.", "The memories I've been trying to suppress have been resurfacing. That means they're still relevant and I need to deal with them."]
